Mansi Joshi

Customer Service Associate

PROFILE

Highly-trained and motivated administrative assistant with over two years of experience. I dig into the customer problems and solve them with modern technology. To accomplish this result I focus on key results and quickly adapt to insights.

EXPERIENCE

Krishna Electrovision Pvt Ltd, -2020-2021

Worked as an Export Executive. The role included handling shipping documents, ensure effective management of the export business, consultation of the clients regarding products, relation participation in sales activity.

Customer Service Associate, Barnes & Nobles, — 2018-2019

Worked in a college during my associates in Cuyahoga Community College.

I esteemed selling products, giving detailed information about the products as well as billing the products.

Additionally, solving glitch for customer with top notch service was also a part of my job.

Computer Assistant, Ambe Vidyalaya, -2016-2017

Assisted the professor for an entire year in High School.

Assisting students to perform certain tasks and how to use computer software or hardware to prevent future problems.

Also, Help students troubleshoot problems with their computers

EDUCATION

Class of March-2017 completed 10+2 with above 50 percentage.- Commerce

Based on merits expected to get Masters in Business Management (Foreign Trade) by 2023

AWARDS

Academic Honor Roll - 2016-2017

The Sprints(100m) - 2004

Hurdling (100m)

Middle Distance Racing(1000m)

HOBBIES

I really like to play Tennis and Basketball in sports.

I enjoy reading books some of my favorites are The Adventures of Huckleberry Finn by Mark Twain, Wuthering Heights by Emily Brontë,

I love to dance as that is something I enjoy from very core of my heart also, I like to travel and do adventure sports very much.

SKILLS

SEO

Microsoft Office Suite

Conversational/Written-English, Hindi, Gujarati

90+ WMP Typist

Customer Service

Public speaking

Accuracy and attention to detail

Adaption and flexibility

Verbal English with accent

F-302 Ganesh Gold, Ahmedabad, Gujarat 382481 <u>mansijoshi049@hotmail.com</u> Ph no. +91 9723272668